Scenic Hudson Collection: Records Relating to the Storm King Case, 1963-1981
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 17. Clippings, 17; About 7 linear feet Boxes: 167 - 183 > Folders: 2418 - 2606
  - Aug. 27 - Sept. 3, 1973 (Folder 2539, Box 179)
  - Sept. 4 - Sept. 11, 1973 (Folder 2540, Box 179)
  - Sept. 12 - Sept. 19, 1973 (Folder 2541, Box 179)
  - Sept. 20 - Sept. 27, 2973 (Folder 2542, Box 179)
  - Sept. 26 - Oct. 5, 1973 (Folder 2543, Box 179)
  - Oct. 6 - Oct. 13, 1973 (Folder 2544, Box 179)
  - Oct. 14 - Oct. 21, 1973 (Folder 2545, Box 179)
  - Oct. 22 - Oct. 29, 1973 (Folder 2546, Box 179)
  - Oct. 30 - Nov. 5, 1973 (Folder 2547, Box 179)
  - Nov. 6 - Nov. 13, 1973 (Folder 2548, Box 179)
  - Nov. 14 - Nov. 21, 1973 (Folder 2549, Box 179)
  - Nov. 22 - Nov. 29, 1973 (Folder 2550, Box 179)
  - Nov. 30 - Dec. 7, 1973 (Folder 2551, Box 179)
  - Dec. 8 - Dec. 15, 1973 (Folder 2552, Box 179)
  - Dec. 16 - Dec. 23, 1973 (Folder 2553, Box 179)
  - Dec. 24 - Dec. 31, 1973 (Folder 2554, Box 179)
  - Undated (1974) (Folder 2555, Box 180)
  - May - Oct. 1973 (Folder 2556, Box 180)
  - Dec. 10 - Dec. 17, 1973 (Folder 2557, Box 180)
  - Dec. 18 - Dec. 25, 1973 (Folder 2558, Box 180)
  - Dec. 26, 1973 - Jan. 2, 1974 (Folder 2559, Box 180)
  - Jan. 3 - Jan. 10, 1974 (Folder 2560, Box 180)
  - Jan. 11 - Jan. 18, 1974 (Folder 2561, Box 180)
  - Jan. 19 - Jan. 26, 1974 (Folder 2562, Box 180)
  - Jan. 27 - Feb. 3, 1974 (Folder 2563, Box 180)
  - Feb. 4 - Feb. 11, 1974 (Folder 2564, Box 180)
  - Feb. 12 - Feb. 19, 1974 (Folder 2565, Box 180)
  - Feb. 20 - Feb. 27, 1974 (Folder 2566, Box 180)
  - Feb. 28 - March 7, 1974 (Folder 2567, Box 180)
  - March - March 15, 1974 (Folder 2568, Box 180)
  - March 16 - March 23, 1974 (Folder 2569, Box 180)
  - March 24 - March 31, 1974 (Folder 2570, Box 180)
  - April 1974 (Folder 2571, Box 180)
  - Clippings, 1973 (Folder 2572, Box 181)
  - Clippings, 1974 (Folder 2573, Box 181)
  - Clippings, 1976-77 (Folder 2574, Box 181)
  - Article 8; 1977-78 (Folder 2575, Box 181)
  - Undated Clippings (Folder 2576, Box 181)
  - Clippings: Cornwall Local (Folder 2577, Box 181)
  - Clippings: Daily News, Newsday, and Pok. Journal (Folder 2578, Box 181)
  - Clippings: Evening News (Folder 2579, Box 181)
  - Clippings: The Harvard Crimson (Folder 2580, Box 181)
  - Clippings: Long Island Press (Folder 2581, Box 181)
  - Clippings: New York Post (Folder 2582, Box 181)
  - Clippings: New York Times (Folder 2583, Box 181)
  - Clippings: Patent Trader (Folder 2584, Box 181)
  - Clippings: Times Herald Record (Folder 2585, Box 181)
  - Corps of Engineers (U.S. Army) (Folder 2586, Box 182)
  - Blackouts (Folder 2587, Box 182)
  - The Great North East Blackout, News Clippings (Folder 2588, Box 182)
  - Con Ed - Pollution (Folder 2589, Box 182)
  - Con Ed (Other Activities) (Folder 2590, Box 182)
  - Cornwall Project - Taxes, etc. (Hudson Valley Project) (Folder 2591, Box 182)
  - Dam Safety (Folder 2592, Box 182)
  - Editorials&Clips (Folder 2593, Box 182)
  - Editorials on Appeals Decision (Folder 2594, Box 182)
  - Fire Island (Folder 2595, Box 182)
  - Generation (Folder 2596, Box 182)
  - Historic (Folder 2597, Box 182)
  - Clippings: Hudson River, Historical Information (Folder 2598, Box 183)
  - Jetport Issue (Folder 2599, Box 183)
  - Power Plants - Problems, etc (Folder 2600, Box 183)
  - Press - Correspondence, etc. (Folder 2601, Box 183)
  - Readers Digest Article; Feb. 1969 (Folder 2602, Box 183)
  - Rockefeller, Gov. Nelson A. - Clippings (Folder 2603, Box 183)
  - Clippings: Travel (Folder 2604, Box 183)
  - Clippings: Wallkill (Power Line) (Folder 2605, Box 183)
  - Underground Plant (Folder 2606, Box 183)
- 18. Oversize Material, 18; About .5 linear feet Box: 184 Folders: 2607 - 2617
  Series contains proofs and layouts of publicity materials..
  - S.H.P.C. Hudson River Layout (Folder 2607, Box 184)
  - Scenic Hudson Layout - Looking for Reversal of Court Decision (Folder 2608, Box 184)
  - Open Letter to Charles Luce - Chairman of the Board for Con Ed (Folder 2609, Box 184)
  - Publicity Layout - SHPC Conservation Organization of the Year, 1969 (Folder 2610, Box 184)
  - Proposed Con Ed Storm King Pumped Storage Project in Hudson Gorge (Folder 2611, Box 184)
  - Map of N.Y.C. and counties north of the city (Folder 2612, Box 184)
  - Clippings (Folder 2613, Box 184)
  - Hudson River - Layout for Publicity (Folder 2614, Box 184)
  - Salute to Storm King Layout, 8/26/69 (Folder 2615, Box 184)
  - OED Galley and Lettering for Emergencies (Folder 2616, Box 184)
  - Long Island Resources Council (Folder 2617, Box 184)
- 19. Card File, 19; About .5 linear feet Box: 185 Folder: 2618
  Series contains file of individuals invited to the Alexander Saunders luncheon, Dec. 9, 1969.
  - Card File - Lists of Organizations (Folder 2618, Box 185)
- 20. Audiovisual Materials, 20; About 0.5 linear feet Boxes: 186 - 187 Folders: 2619 - 2635
  Series contains tapes, films, and still photographs are housed at the end of the collection.
  Roughly Chronological
  - Tape: “Meeting with Scenic Hudson Group, Monday, June 6, 1964 (Folder 186 A, Box 186)
  - Crisis on Our Rivers (Folder 186 B, Box 186)
  - CBS News - Selvage; Lee, Inc. Mr. Egen (Folder 186 C, Box 186)
  - Films: Hudson Highlands - Aerial Footage, Oct. 1964 Congressman Ottinger (Folder 186 D, Box 186)
  - World at Ten (Folder 186 E, Box 186)
  - Videos 1 and 1a - News Story about Proposed plant at Storm King, Man interviewed in front of Plant Model&World at Ten News Story About Con Ed Proposed Plant…In Studio Discussion w/ P.R. and Author Carl Carmer (Folder 2623, Box 186A)
  - Videos 2 and 2a - Man Talking Possibly about Storm King and Marist College, Aerials of Storm King -Marist College,& Crisis on Our Rivers, NYS Dept. of Health (Folder 2624, Box 186A)
  - Release w/ Photo of Storm King Mountain (Folder 2625, Box 187)
  - Clippings&Photos of Mt. Beacon (Folder 2626, Box 187)
  - Hudson River Fisheries - We Need Your Help Now (Folder 2627, Box 187)
  - Oct. 1968 Con Ed’s Backbone Transmission System, Map (Negative) from FPC Staff Brief (Folder 2628, Box 187)
  - FPC Exhibit 246-R, Waring Exhibit #9 (Folder 2629, Box 187)
  - Waring Exhibits #’s 6, 7, 7A, and 8 (Folder 2630, Box 187)
  - Scenic Hudson - Storm King Project Photos (Folder 2631, Box 187)
  - Storm King Highway Photos (Folder 2632, Box 187)
  - Storm King Photos (Copies) (Folder 2633, Box 187)
  - Negatives and Photos - Exhibits (Folder 2634, Box 187)
  - Photo of Rod Vandivert SHPC Board Member (Folder 2635, Box 187)
  - Misc. Photos (Folder 2636, Box 187)